[{"answer": "Good to be with you.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "If he's reunited the whole of America, including you, this is a good step forward, isn't it?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Well, ideally, sure.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Do you think they should live up to their rhetoric?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, if we're going to apply that standard, Joe Biden has to resign this evening because he has said enough different goofy things over time that you couldn't possibly remain vice president.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "So by his own words, he is no longer qualified to be president, is he, Mr. Speaker?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I think he's got to do two things and I think they're pretty clear but pretty hard.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "But if he's going to seal the deal, Mitt Romney, and actually win this election, what's he got to do now?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "That must be a failure by the Romney campaign, isn't it?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, Piers.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Governor, how are you?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Very well.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "How about you?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's about time but it's really only part of the story.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "How are you reacting to Mitt Romney's tax returns which have landed this Friday afternoon?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Absolutely staggering amount, isn't it?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "What do you mean by that?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "I think the bigger issue about the failure to release his tax returns, he must know that most Americans would react with some horror at the degree to which he's used tax avoidance schemes and Cayman Island bank accounts and the like to avoid paying the full amount of taxes that he should.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Is there anything ethically wrong with what he's been doing?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "It seems to me just looking at them, anyone that gives $4 million to charity in one year, you can hardly accuse him of milking the system too much, can you?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "That's the real message when you dig into the tax returns that have been released, is the tremendous sophistication and expense required to effectively avoid taxes as well as he has.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "I mean, is that the bottom line?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "I think Henry's right.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Henry Rosen, what do you make of this?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "My guess is Harry Reid would feel better if he actually saw the returns instead of a letter from a bunch of accountants swearing that Mitt Romney paid taxes.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Doesn't Harry Reid have to stand up now and issue a public apology to Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "You're saying the accountants are lying?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Well, I think his entire economic plan has been based on the idea that we have to give more money to the job creators, the investors and the entrepreneurs.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "So how do you think this plays out for the election?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Do you ever wish that Mitt Romney was worth about 300 million less, that he was like a regular guy with a regular income, maybe worth three million dollars?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "That's a lot to assume.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Are you or are you not?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Let me ask you a direct question.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Where do you get off?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I don't know what that is.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Are you or have you ever been a liberal?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm a conservative.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Are you a conservative?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "I would categorize Kenny as an independent actually.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Would you categorize him as more of a liberal?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Do you vote?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "I have always voted for the best person, the one that moved me, that I felt would inspire me, would inspire everything else around me.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Who do you vote for normally?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Ladies and gentlemen, piers Morgan receives a hug.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Why do I feel I'm losing control of this interview?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Is it time for a commercial break, he cries out desperately.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "My God, is that the first time anyone's hugged you in your life?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I can tell you the issues that -- we tour like crazy, 60 some odd cities this year, all over the United States.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Parking who you actually vote for to one side, what are the issues that you really are divided over, would you say?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "I find that a fatuous argument.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "You going to outlaw alcohol and cars?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "ORGAN: You would shoot them dead?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "I know what a hillbilly is.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "You know what a hillbilly is, Piers?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I did when it came out, sure, because I remember where I was when I heard the term the first time.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Something that's dogged you for years afterward?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Go to Vegas for the weekend, yeah.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Did you ever make up with Rob Lowe, like the old -- like Dean, Sammy, Frank, you all hang out together?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "I never met Charlie Sheen.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "You ever party with Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Well, it first started happening as a reaction to all that stuff you were just talking about.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "What drives you?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "The more I traveled the world, the more I realized America is a great place.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Did it change your perspective of America too?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Look, come on, Piers.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "What was that all about?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "I learned that you can't really reconcile the two.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What did you learn about yourself in reality?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "But do you to complete strangers in Patagonia?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Look, I come back from some trips and she goes, Jesus, we're just getting the rhythm.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Wake up every morning and say, is he still here?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think to a large degree.", "docId": "120921pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Does she accept you are just a nomad, that's the way you're going to be?", "qSentId": 561}]